A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Our battle to stop the Kishans' revival was drawn to a close.
Death Scythe and I wanted to end our fight with Medusa as quickly as possible so we could continue on and help the others.
But Medusa knew that was our plan, and she did everything she could to draw the struggle out longer.
After I hit Medusa with my sole wavelength, we found ourselves in a deadlock.
Neither of us could take a single step. One movement could mean death.
Meanwhile, Kid and his group fought one last battle against Erika and Free in an attempt to stop the Kishans' revival.
Take this!
Erika!
She's got the blood!
Kid and Blackstar tried to destroy the syringe that Medusa had filled with black blood.
Erika was attempting to inject the black blood into the Kishan.
At first, it appeared that Blackstar had succeeded in shattering the syringe that would wake the Kishan.
But unfortunately, Blackstar had been hallucinating.
We failed?
At that moment, Medusa let her guard down, and our battle ended.
Medusa let her guard down, and our battle ended.
And then it happened.
The Kishan awoke.
Let's go.
Damn, that's annoying.
What is it, Blackstar?
That thing's the Kishin?
Tsubaki, Enchanted Sword Mode.
We're gonna kill this thing now.
I can't. Your body already took too much of a beating earlier.
If we do Enchanted Sword anymore, then I could easily end up cutting off a piece of your soul.
Shut up and do what I say! Now hurry! Enchanted Sword Mode!
I can't do it!
Fine, you can sit here and watch.
Blackstar!
Come on, we're going too.
Okay!
Yeah!
Take this, creepy naked demon pervert!
Blackstar, big wave!
My body can't even endure my own wavelength.
You're gonna die!
Blackstar!
Damn it!
Oh, my God.
I'm naked. This is so wrong. I need to cover up. I like the macho look.
Does he mean me?
Where'd he go?
Maka!
Come back here!
This is great!
Awesome!
Let's see some more.
Hot, hot. Amazing.
What a catfight.
Dream come true.
Get the hell off me.
Come on, you're a witch, aren't you?
Why don't you use magic?
I will if you do, stupid cat.
You're heavy. Move already.
Oh, shut up. You need to go back to the sewers where you belong.
This is too much.
Hey, anyone else feel the shaking?
Maybe you're just too excited.
No, the ground really is shaking.
Aw, is the poor mousey shaking?
How pathetic.
Idiot.
It's the ground shaking, not me.
What, is it an earthquake?
Gee, it looks like Erika and the others succeeded.
Look, what's that up there?
Something came out from underground.
That thing is Asherah?
Marka!
I have to...
stop the...
Kishin.
You're something else.
You know that, right?
What now?
We've got more company?
Whoa, what are those?
Are those...
Death's seals are still alive.
And after all these years...
What is that...
thing?
Well, at least the Kishin left us a nice big hole.
It did make it a lot easier to get up here.
Ribbit.
Hey, look.
Something's caught him.
Probably some of Death's seals that were activated.
Will he be okay?
Those seals have been around too long.
They won't hold a newly reborn Kishin.
Tore him apart like scrap paper.
Hmm.
Uh, never mind that now.
Free, look.
There's a problem.
Hey, everyone!
What is it, Erika?
You're spelled, Free.
You told us it would last for a whole hour.
But it's wearing off after only 40 minutes.
I guess I may have exaggerated about the time a little bit.
I'm a man after all.
We do show off sometimes.
It's you.
Hello, Death.
Hi-ya.
Long time no see, huh?
You doing okay?
You look all skinny and frail.
And I know how much you like your heavy clothing.
You must not be very comfortable in that outfit.
It seems you've changed, too.
What's with that ridiculous mask?
Yeah, it is kind of different, huh?
You see, after I stuffed you into that bag, I started an academy for meisters and weapons.
My old mask would scare the kids senseless, so I had to make a little change.
It was really bad.
The little ones would even start crying.
Those seals are pretty scary, too, actually.
Everything from the old days seems to be.
I take it that's also why you talk in a funny voice now.
Yes, I've grown quite used to all of it over the years.
Now, I'm sorry to do this right after you've woken up.
But it's time for you to die again.
Reaper!
Tell me, Death.
Do you know the pain of having all of your skin torn off, ripped from your entire body?
I've actually forgotten how it felt myself.
Try to make me remember!
Shockwaves, huh?
My turn.
Let's see how you like this.
What is all this?
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
Split up and help anyone who's injured.
Oh, right.
Gather all of the civilians and lead them out of town.
You got it?
Yes, sir!
A full-scale battle between those two could very well blow away all of Death City.
Lord Death, we're counting on you.
You're not going anywhere.
Whoa, now that is cool.
He hasn't reached full strength yet, but I don't have my death size.
He may be able to strike a blow that would finish me off for good.
Get out of the way!
Push her off!
You can't stop me now!
Lord Death, no!
You filthy, unforgivable swine!
That's it.
I'm going to skin you alive again!
They bounced away?
But how?
You deflected my attack?
Damn you, shrewd demon!
You knew there was a boundary past which my attacks wouldn't be able to hit you?
I doubt we'll ever be meeting again.
Goodbye, Master.
It's been fun.
Thank you,
the students who went underground to fight right we'll need reinforcements
contact the death size that are scattered across the continents tell them to gather quickly yes sir
to think a keishan would revive on today of all days the anniversary celebration of the academy
i built to prevent the creation of more keishans things are about to get very busy
we should be safe here for now who is this chick anyway a combination of five misenies
oh okay i can't sense medusa's magic anymore i guess that means she died in there
i just have one regret i didn't get to see her die
in a way though i suppose i did kind of look up to her there aren't many witches of her caliber out
there funny huh
it looks like lord death and the keishan were fighting it out up here
but the madness seems to be fading
he got away
i wish i could have seen it if only i'd stayed by lord death's side like i'm always supposed to
then we could have stopped him things turned out horribly and what's worse everyone will blame me
there's no use crying over spilt milk spirit besides this isn't over yet if we can't figure out a way
to make this right we'll have a lot more problems than your ego
stein
damn
i love you you know a man after my own heart
don't be stupid at your core medusa you're just like me you can't possibly understand a concept like
love
what kind of woman would be willing to extinguish your own soul
what kind of woman would be your Ontor?
4.000
girl
You can't imagine how disastrous it will be if the Kishan is revived again.
Its madness will spread like a plague.
It has been a very long night, indeed.
An exhausting, difficult night that felt at times like it would go on forever.
And yet, not all is hopeless.
Even after a night like this, morning will eventually come.
What? What? What?
What? What?
What?
はじまるよ、君とぼくを
つなぐ扉の奥
すればどんな未来が
ぶくらを待っているの?
Oh
is
See you next time.
Oh, breath of fresh air is certainly nice.
Hey, Mr. Kishin, it must feel good to be outside after all this time.
What do you want to do first?
Stretch.
What did you want to do most while you were sealed up in that bag?
What did you do for fun as a child?
Stretch.
Hobbies?
Stretching.
Special skills?
What's your dream?
To stretch.
How do you move a hurt person?
Stretcher.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the Death Scythes convene.
Stop Dad's staff reassignment?
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.